[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Розмова, діалог' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はなし"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Показувати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "みせます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Починати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はじめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Пояснювати, повідомляти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おしえます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Адреса' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じゅう, しょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Йти (опади)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふります"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Ім*я' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "なまえ"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Одразу' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "すぐ"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Сіль' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しお"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Цукор' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さとう"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'Робити копію' read in word?",
        "answer": "コピーします"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'Знову' read in word?",
        "answer": "また"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'Повільно' read in word?",
        "answer": "ゆっくり"
    }
]
